<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>The Five W's</title>
    <link>https://pulcherrimumquaerere.com/Pages/poems/the-five-ws.html</link>
    <description>
        This is one of my newest poems that I've written. It follows me
        asking myself the five w's. Who, What, When, Where and Why. The
        constant theme is me questioning who is to blame for my abuse as a
        child. As well as me expressing the anger I hold towards my parents.
        I do love them dearly, but there are things I have yet to forgive
        them over.
    </description>
    <language>en-us</language>

    <item>
      <title>A Life</title>
      <link>https://pulcherrimumquaerere.com/Pages/poems/a-life.html</link>
      <description>
        This is probably one of my favorite and longest poems. It takes you
        thought my first suicide attempt and the following years that I
        suffer with depression. I'm happy to be in a better place today but
        it doesn't hurt to know where you've been.
      </description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Breaking Point</title>
      <link>https://pulcherrimumquaerere.com/Pages/poems/breaking-point.html</link>
      <description>
        This poem I actually started writing during work. It's about many
        issues I go through. The main theme of the poem is about
        the sexual abuse I suffered through my childhood.
      </description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Fear</title>
      <link>https://pulcherrimumquaerere.com/Pages/poems/fear.html</link>
      <description>
        While the name is <i>Fear</i>, the poem isn't actually about anything
        I fear. Most people fear the unknown. So take the side of me that I
        keep hidden from my friends, family, and world. It's unknown and
        to be naturally feared.
      </description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Forgoten</title>
      <link>https://pulcherrimumquaerere.com/Pages/poems/forgoten.html</link>
      <description>
        Here I tried to capture what I like to forget. So when I refer to my
        pain, I do so with the hopes that I won't think of it until I'm ready.
      </description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Grief</title>
      <link>https://pulcherrimumquaerere.com/Pages/poems/grief.html</link>
      <description>
        You know how sometimes you'll take the scenic route on a roadtrip?
        This is how I address the way I grieve with my first suicide attempt.
        Recalling the way I felt and what was going through my mind.
      </description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>I'm Tired</title>
      <link>https://pulcherrimumquaerere.com/Pages/poems/im-tired.html</link>
      <description>
        So many things in the world bother me. Many happen over and over,
        or in some cases, are just ignored. Read me talk about this in my poem.
      </description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Malnourished</title>
      <link>https://pulcherrimumquaerere.com/Pages/poems/malnourished.html</link>
      <description>
        At the time of writing this I was in a relationship and going through
        a rough patch. In retrospect, I failed at communicating properly. Yet
        in the moment I looked at my ex and saw them as not loving me in the
        way I needed most. So why include something like this? It's art.
      </description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>